Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
Huo Beishan found me…
وجدني هوو بيشان...
The…
ال…
The young lady you love…
الفتاة التي تحبها...
Is her name Huo Qingwan?
هل اسمها هوو تشينغوان؟
Remember,
يتذكر،
everyone in the Huo family
الجميع في عائلة هوو
is our enemy.
هو عدونا.
You can never be together…
لا يمكن أن تكونوا معًا أبدًا
Can we never be together, after all?
هل يمكننا أن نكون معًا أبدًا، بعد كل شيء؟
=Episode 12=
=الحلقة 12=
(Tomb of Huang Li)
(قبر هوانغ لي)
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
She was the only family I had left in this world.
لقد كانت عائلتي الوحيدة التي بقيت في هذا العالم.
You can tell me her story.
يمكنك أن تخبرني قصتها.
You'll feel better.
سوف تشعر بتحسن.
She was my mother's maid.
لقد كانت خادمة والدتي.
They were like sisters.
لقد كانوا مثل الأخوات.
She took care of me
لقد اهتمت بي
after my mother passed away.
بعد وفاة والدتي.
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
please bear with it.
من فضلك تحمل ذلك.
Whenever I was mistreated in the Huo family,
كلما تعرضت لسوء المعاملة في عائلة هوو،
she was the one who stood by me.
لقد كانت هي التي وقفت بجانبي.
Only she never
فقط هي لم تفعل ذلك ابدا
forgot my mother.
نسيت أمي.
♪We switch our roles♪
♪نحن نبدل الأدوار♪
♪Darkness fades, and daylight breaks♪
♪يتلاشى الظلام، ويشرق ضوء النهار♪
♪Evening winds usher in the night♪
♪رياح المساء تبشر بقدوم الليل♪
She loved chestnuts,
كانت تحب الكستناء،
so I buried her under a chestnut tree.
لذلك دفنتها تحت شجرة الكستناء.
I'm sure
انا متأكد
Madam Li will be happy to see it
السيدة لي ستكون سعيدة برؤيته
when the chestnuts ripen and fall next year.
عندما تنضج الكستناء وتسقط في العام المقبل.
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪
After tonight,
بعد الليلة،
no matter how hard it gets, you have to hold it together.
بغض النظر عن مدى صعوبة الأمر، عليك أن تتماسك.
Governor can't find out.
المحافظ لا يستطيع معرفة ذلك.
I don't know
لا أعرف
what happened to your mother,
ماذا حدث لأمك؟
but you have to pretend everything's normal
لكن عليك أن تتظاهر بأن كل شيء طبيعي
if you want to stay safe.
إذا كنت تريد البقاء آمنًا.
Don't push me away.
لا تدفعني بعيدا.
You're the only one I have left.
أنت الشخص الوحيد الذي بقي لي.
Huang Li is dead.
لقد مات هوانغ لي.
Liu Chengyin.
ليو تشينجين.
Weilian!
ويليان!
Weilian, I was wrong.
ويليان، لقد كنت مخطئا.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Is this all because of Huo Qingwan?
هل كل هذا بسبب هوو تشينغوان؟
Sheng Weilian!
شنغ ويليان!
You ruined me!
لقد دمرتني!
You can't abandon me!
لا يمكنك أن تتخلى عني!
Leave me alone!
اتركني وحدي!
You'll actually do whatever it takes
سوف تفعل كل ما يلزم في الواقع
to get into the Sheng family, huh?
للدخول إلى عائلة شنغ، هاه؟
I'll prove to you
سأثبت لك
I'm better for you
أنا أفضل لك
than Huo Qingwan ever was.
مما كان عليه هوه تشينغوان في أي وقت مضى.
Then, I'll be waiting to see
ثم سأنتظر لأرى
just how worthy you are of my love.
كم أنت جدير بحبي.
(Huo Residence)
(سكن هوو)
Can't you tell me
ألا يمكنك أن تخبرني؟
who you really are?
من أنت حقا؟
Didn't you say
ألم تقل؟
it didn't matter who I was?
لم يهم من أنا؟
I hate the Huo family.
أنا أكره عائلة هوو.
But I think
ولكنني أعتقد
you're different from the rest of them.
أنت مختلف عن الباقي منهم.
Maybe you and I
ربما أنت وأنا
are alike in some ways.
متشابهان في بعض النواحي.
I used to want
كنت أريد
to do one thing above all else.
أن أفعل شيئاً واحداً فوق كل شيء آخر.
But now I realize
ولكن الآن أدركت
that thing
هذا الشيء
could cost me what matters most.
ربما يكلفني الأمر الأكثر أهمية.
Do you think I should go through with it?
هل تعتقد أنني يجب أن أفعل هذا؟
If it's something
إذا كان شيئا
that has to be done, then you must accept losing what matters to you.
إذا كان عليك أن تفعل هذا، فعليك أن تقبل خسارة ما يهمك.
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Be careful.
احرص.
Cui.
أيّ.
Why are you moving all these things?
لماذا تحرك كل هذه الأشياء؟
Governor wants the warehouse demolished.
المحافظ يطالب بهدم المستودع
Miss, don't go over there.
آنسة، لا تذهبي إلى هناك.
Someone died here.
لقد مات شخص هنا.
It's haunted.
إنه مسكون.
Someone died here?
هل مات أحد هنا؟
Qingwan,
تشينغوان،
Uncle wants us to have lunch together.
عمي يريد منا أن نتناول الغداء معًا.
You should get changed.
ينبغي عليك التغيير.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪